leaderu.com 2007-06-30

# Leadership University Privacy Policy

Leadership University takes all possible measures to protect the personal information of its users. We store any personal data given to us as securely as possible, and NEVER sell, rent, give or otherwise provide that personal data (including e-mail address) to anyone outside of our organization. Leadership University is sponsored by Christian Leadership Ministries, the faculty outreach and training arm of Campus Crusade for Christ International. 

We leverage leading technologies and practices for e-commerce to ensure the privacy and security of your information and online transactions. This privacy policy explains how we collectand use your personal information.

**Information Collection**

We collect your personal information in order to enhance your experience on the Leadership University web site and to improve the quality of our services. 

**Web Site Users and Donors**

We use various online forms to collect information which includes, but is not limited to, name, mailing address, phone number, email address, credit card number, and credit card expiration date. We may collect profile information such as preferences or interests. We invite users to provide feedback to us.

**Information Use**

If you donate to Campus Crusade for Christ through Leadership University, we use your information to process your donation(s), to verify your credit card data, and to send you a receipt. We may contact you again about a similar opportunity. You may request to be removed at any time. 

If you choose to have us send you information, we may use your email address or your mailing address to communicate with you about the operation Campus Crusade for Christ, to inform you about our ministry, products and services or to send you information that we think might be of interest to you.

Christian Leadership Ministries (Campus Crusade for Christ) does not sell, rent, or trade your personal information to others. Furthermore, we will not share your information with others without your consent. 

In general, we use your information, usually in aggregate, to operate our site, to analyze our site to make it more effective, to improve the products and services that we offer you, and for other general ministry purposes. 

**Internet Protocol Addresses and Cookies**

We collect non-personal information from you with "Internet Protocol (IP) addresses" and "cookies" to help us administer and improve our Web sites, and to provide a customized experience for you on our Web sites. An IP address is a numeric address assigned to your computer. The IP address is not linked to any personally identifiable information, so your name remains anonymous. We use IP addresses to track how users use our web sites, to administer our system, and to improve security. 

Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your web browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies allow the web site to store and reference specific types of information while you are visiting a site. We may use cookies to manage your experience on our web sites and to store items between your visits. Our cookies contain no personal or financial information. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, though browser preferences may be changed to prevent this if the user so desires.

**Security**

Our web sites employ security measures to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. When make donations or reveal sensitive information, we use a secure server to protect the security of your online transactions. Your information is transmitted using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), the industry standard for sending encrypted information. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access. 

If you choose to receive email or mail from Leadership University, but later decide that you no longer want to, we provide clear instructions on how to remove your name.

**Other**

By using the Leadership University web site, you consent to our collection and use of the personal information you provide. Please note that if at any time Christian Leadership Ministries (Campus Crusade for Christ) is required by law or a legal process to release individual or organizational information, we must cooperate fully.

If our privacy policy changes, we will post any changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

**Questions**

If you have any questions or comments about this privacy statement, please contact us:

By email: 

By regular mail: Christian Leadership Ministries  
P.O. Box 129  
Addison, TX 75001
